

Krzysztof Wilczyński

Software Engineer with background in QA

Mobile: +48 889 288 172

Email: krzysztof.marek.wilczynski@gmail.com

My frontend projects:

https://kwilczyn.github.io/kw/projects/

Summary

Experienced software engineer with a strong background in automated testing. I possess solid programming skills in Python and JavaScript. I know how to cover my code with reliable unit, integration and E2E tests.

I have worked with frameworks such as Django and Vue.js.

My skills in CI/CD, Docker, and Amazon Web Services complement my profile as a versatile developer.

Please, find more details about me on my showcase page:

https://kwilczyn.github.io/kw/

Education

Computer Science, MASTER

Wrocław University of Technology, 2015

Automation And Robotics, BACHELOR

Wrocław University of Technology, 2013

Hobbies

Japanese Culture PC gaming

Professional Experience

Software Engineer in Test, Perceptyx sp. z o.o. (HR)

- Technical-leading of Test Automation team
- Implementing E2E tests (pytest-bdd, Selenium, JavaScript)
- Implementing Integration Tests (pytest, REST)
- Preparing new pipelines and maintenance of the existing ones (GitLab Runner)
- Integration of reporting tools (Allure, Testmo)
- Preparing load tests scripts (Python, Locust)
- Identifying bugs and reporting them (**Jira**)
- Supporting the development team in fixing defects (Python, Vue.js, CSS)

Senior Test Design Engineer, Etteplan sp. z o.o. (IoT)

01.2019 - 12.2020

01.2021 - 02.2024

- Implementing E2E tests (Python, RobotFramework, JavaScript)
- Implementing Mobile tests (Appium)
- Administrating of CI Server (Jenkins, Docker)
- Preparation and maintenance of test environments (Vagrant, Virtualbox)
- Preparation of Test Reports (**Testlink**)

Software Test Designer, Etteplan sp. z o.o. (IoT)

07.2016 - 12.2018

- Implementing of E2E tests (RobotFramework, Python, JavaScript)
- Writing Performance tests in JMeter
- Finding and Reporting Bugs (**Jira**)

Software Tester, InTENSO – IT Experts (Banking)

03.2014 - 06.2016

- Team leadership
- Preparation of Test Plans (**Testlink**)
- Scripting (Python, Selenium, PL/SQL, VBA)
- Identifying and reporting bugs (Jira)

Certificates & Courses

Opanuj Frontend

2024, Przeprogramowani (https://opanujfrontend.pl/)

ISTQB FOUNDATION LEVEL

2016, SJSI/Polish Testing Board

Skills

Technologies

JavaScript, Vue.js, Python, pytest, Django, Git, REST, AWS, Docker, Gitlab Runner, Jenkins, Playwright, RobotFramework, Selenium, HTML, CSS

Languages

Polish - Native, English - B2, German - A2